hey guys this is a very short video
announcing the very first rebel wisdom
QA so what we'd love is if you write
your questions in the comments below
this video and we will answer them on
Thursday so you can ask about anything
we've recently put out our latest
podcast about the Jordan Peterson sam
Harris talk there's been some really
high-quality comments already and it
feels like there is a sort of little
community starting to build around the
content we're putting out which is great
something we really want to encourage
and if you guys have any got got any
ideas about how to encourage that a
little bit more we're pretty new to this
we made our first film in January and
we're still learning so if you've got
any suggestions for how to build
community how to start creating the kind
of conversation that we want to see
we're really open to those kind of
questions and any advice ultimately I
think what we're looking for is to
create a space to have a genuinely
generative conversation about some of
the most interesting and important
philosophical cultural questions that
are going on at the moment and I guess
that's why we're sort of why we were
interested in Jordan Peterson why we're
interested in the intellectual dark web
because especially the intellectual dark
web feels like it's a way of trying to
have to carve out a space to be able to
have these kind of conversations in
public like you don't have to agree you
may have very different views but how do
we have conversations that feel like
people are open-minded that they have
the possibility of change in their mind
of learning of and that's the energy
that we want to bring and that's the
energy that we're inviting you guys to
bring as well so ask your questions like
the comments dislike the comments and we
will yeah well we'll answer that will
allow you guys to select which questions
we answer on Thursday thank you very
much